Guide to the Gotham Inc. Records, 1967-1997 and undated RL.00468
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1973-1996 and undated, 129 boxes
  - Major Clients, 1973-1996 and undated
    - Thompson Medical,1986-1993 and undated
      - Aspercreme (continued), 1988-1992 (Box 101)
        - 1710. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Aspercreme. TSAC 2055 Regis :15; TSAC 2065 Regis A :15 NBC/CBS :15. 1992 (Box 101)
      - Cardi-Omega 3, 1987
        - 1711. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cardi Omega 3. XYLC 7653 Child ABC :30; XYLC 7663 Child NBC :30. 1987 (Box 101)
        - 1712. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cardi Omega 3. XYLC 7403 Grandchild NBC :30; XYLC 7423 GrandChild ABC :30. 1987 (Box 101)
        - 1713. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cardi Omega 3. XYLC 7633 Grandchild ABC/Eckerd :30; XYLC 7643 NBC Eckerd :30. 1987 (Box 101)
        - 1714. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cardi Omega 3. XYLC 7653 Child ABC :30; XYLC 7663 Child NBC :30. 1987 (Box 101)
        - 1715. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cardi Omega 3. XYLC 7495 Grandchild NBC Rev.2 :30; XYLC 7505 grandchild ABC Rev.2 :30. 1987 (Box 101)
      - Cortizone, 1987-1991 (Box 102)
        - 1716. Rosenfeld Sirowitz Humphrey & Strauss. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 5. TSCZ 7025 Itch Relief-ABC :15; TSCZ 7035 Itch Relief-ABC :15; TSCZ 7013 Itch Relief :30. 1987 (Box 102)
        - 1717. Rosenfeld Sirowitz Humphrey & Strauss. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 5. XTVH 3073 Arm Exam :30; TSCZ 7013 Itch Relief Rough Cut :30. 1987 (Box 102)
        - 1718. Saatchi & Saatchi Compton. Thompson Medical. Fiber Full Cortizone 5. XTVZ 6013 By Nature/Arm Exam :30. 1987 (Box 102)
        - 1719. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 5. TSCA 8065 Itch Relief :15. 1988 (Box 102)
        - 1720. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 5. TSCA 8065 Sato Time Ring. 1988 (Box 102)
        - 1721. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 5. TSCA 8075 Itch Relief :15. 1988 (Box 102)
        - 1722. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 5. TSCA 7083 Itch Relief Rev. :30. 1988 (Box 102)
        - 1723. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 5. TSCA 7083 Itch Relief Rev. :30. 1988 (Box 102)
        - 1724. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 1185 Medical Update/A :15. 1991 (Box 102)
        - 1725. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 1203 Medical Update/Free Offer A :30. 1991 (Box 102)
        - 1726. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 1293 Medical Update W/Out Offer B :30. 1991 (Box 102)
        - 1727. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 1185 Medical Update A :15. 1991 (Box 102)
        - 1728. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 1185 Medical Update A :15. 1991 (Box 102)
        - 1729. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 5. TSCZ 8065 Itch Relief Rev.A CBS/NBC :15; TSCZ 8075 Itch Relief Rev.A ABC :15. 1991 (Box 102)
        - 1730. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 1203 Medical Update/Free Offer A :30. 1991 (Box 102)
        - 1731. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 5. TSCZ 8065 Itch Relief Rev.A CBS/NBC :15; TSCZ 8075 Itch Relief Rev.A ABC :15. 1991 (Box 102)
      - Cortizone (continued), 1991-1993 (Box 103)
        - 1732. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 1213 Medical Update W/Out Offer A :30. 1991 (Box 103)
        - 1733. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 1185 Medical Update A :15. 1991 (Box 103)
        - 1734. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 1283 Medical Update/Free Offer B :30. 1991 (Box 103)
        - 1735. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 1293 Medical Update W/Out Offer B :30. 1991 (Box 103)
        - 1736. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 5. TSCZ 1115 Itch Relief Rev.5/ CBS NBC Vers. :15. 1992 (Box 103)
        - 1737. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 2453 Itchy Rash/Free Offer :30. 1992 (Box 103)
        - 1738. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 2433 Itchy Rash B :30. 1992 (Box 103)
        - 1739. Ad Lib. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. External Anal Itch Relief. TSCX 2075 8 Out Of 10--B :15. 1992 (Box 103)
        - 1740. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 2433 Itchy Rash B :30. 1992 (Box 103)
        - 1741. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 2453 Itchy Rash/Free Offer :30. 1992 (Box 103)
        - 1742. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 2463 Itchy Rash C :30. 1992 (Box 103)
        - 1743. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 2463 Itchy Rash C :30. 1992 (Box 103)
        - 1744. Ad Lib. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. External Anal Itch Relief. TSCX 2075 8 out of 10--B :15; TSCT 3493 Itchy Rash/Ext. Tag/CC :30. 1992 (Box 103)
        - 1745. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone for Kids. TSCK 3075 Intro/New Tag W/O Music :30. 1993 (Box 103)
        - 1746. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 3493 Itch Rash/Ext. Tag/CC :30. 1993 (Box 103)
        - 1747. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone for Kids. TSCK 3053 Kids Intro Rev./CC :30. 1993 (Box 103)
      - Cortizone (continued), 1993 (Box 104)
        - 1748. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone for Kids. TSCK 3053 Kids Intro Rev./CC :30. 1993 (Box 104)
        - 1749. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 3493 Itchy Rash/Ext Tag :30. 1993 (Box 104)
        - 1750. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone for Kids. TSCk 3073 Intro/New Tag W/o music :30. 1993 (Box 104)
        - 1751. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 3493 Itchy Rash/Ext. Tag/CC :30. 1993 (Box 104)
        - 1752. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone for Kids. TSCK 3073 Intro New Tag W/o music :30. 1993 (Box 104)
        - 1753. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone for Kids. TSCK 2043 Kids Intro :30. 1993 (Box 104)
        - 1754. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone for Kids. TSCK 3053 Kids Intro/Rev. :30. 1993 (Box 104)
        - 1755. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone 10. TSCT 2463 Itchy Rash C :30. 1993 (Box 104)
        - 1756. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Cortizone for Kids. TSCK 2043 Kids Intro :30. 1993 (Box 104)
      - Dexatrim, 1986-1987
        - 1757. Saatchi & Saatchi Compton. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. XTVD 5803 3 Demos :30. 1986 (Box 104)
        - 1758. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. Three Women :30 Edited Master. 1986 (Box 104)
        - 1759. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. XTVD 6123 Graphics Del/Rio Capsule Rev. :30. 1986 (Box 104)
        - 1760. Momar. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. XTVD 7563 Fact Flanagan Rev. III/Arm Exam :30; XTVD 7553 Fact Elich Rev. III Arm Exam :30. 1987 (Box 104)
        - 1761. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. XTVD 7475 Fact/Elich Rev.III :15; XTVD 7485 Fact/Flanigan Rev.III :15. 1987 (Box 104)
        - 1762. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. Undated (Box 104)
        - 1763. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. 5-30 Sec. Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 104)
      - Dexatrim (continued), 1987-1988 (Box 105)
        - 1764. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 7163 No diet/Clinical :30. 1987 (Box 105)
        - 1765. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 7143 No Diet/Water :30. 1987 (Box 105)
        - 1766. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Dexatrim. 4 spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 105)
        - 1767. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. XTVD 7435 Fact/Elich Rev.1 :15; XTVD 7445 Fact/Flanagan Rev.1 :15. 1987 (Box 105)
        - 1768. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. XTVD 6223 Morning to Midnight Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 105)
        - 1769. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. 5 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 105)
        - 1770. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Dexatrim. XTVD 7923 No Diet II Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 105)
        - 1771. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Dexatrim. XTVD 7923 No Diet II Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 105)
        - 1772. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Dexatrim. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 105)
        - 1773. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. XTVD 7325 No Diet/Elich Alone :15. 1987 (Box 105)
        - 1774. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. XTVD 7355 No Diet/Flanagan Alone :15. 1987 (Box 105)
        - 1775. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. 5 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 105)
        - 1776. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. XTVD 7265; XTVD 7255; XTVD 7245 :15 each. 1987 (Box 105)
        - 1777. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX I lost Weight & Feel Great Rev.3 :30; TSDX 8775 I Lost Weight & Feel Great Rev.2 :15. 1988 (Box 105)
        - 1778. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 7235 No Diet/Fairbanks :15; TSDX 7245 No Diet/Waters :15. 1988 (Box 105)
        - 1779. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 7223 No Diet/Waters Caffeine Free :30. 1988 (Box 105)
      - Dexatrim (continued), 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1780. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Dexatrim. TSDX 8415 Today/Caffeine :15. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1781. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8533 Scroll today Rev.II :30. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1782. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8543 Scroll/Today/Caplet :30. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1783. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Dexatrim Caplets. TSDX 8293 Look At Her :30; TSDX 8303 Look At Her :30. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1784. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8445 Caffeine Anne :15. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1785. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8563 Scroll Today Rev.3 :30. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1786. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. 4 spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1787. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim Caplets. TSDX 8303 Look At Her Alt. Rev. :30. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1788. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 4736 No Matter How :60; TSDX 8670 News Report 2:00. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1789. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Dexatrim. TSDX 8293 Look at Her :30; TSDX 8303 Look at Her :30; No Code Everyone Knows :30. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1790. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8533 Scroll Today Rev.II :30. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1791. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim Caplets. TSDX 8343 Look at Her Mortise :30. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1792. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8455 Caffeine Anne :15. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1793. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8433 Scroll Today Rev. A; TSDX 8405 Today :15. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1794. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8543 Scroll Today Caplet :30. 1988 (Box 106)
        - 1795. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8393 Scroll Today Caffeine :30. 1988 (Box 106)
      - Dexatrim (continued), 1988-1989 (Box 107)
        - 1796. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Dexatrim Caplets. TSDX 8293 Look at Her :30; TSDX 8303 Look At Her :30. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1797. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Dexatrim Caplets. 4-30 Sec Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1798. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 7235 No Diet Fairbanks :15; TSDX 7245 No Diet Waters :15. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1799. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. 4-30 Sec Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1800. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8433 Scroll Today Rev.A. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1801. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8423 Scroll Today Rev. :30; TSDX 8405 Scroll Today Rev. :15. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1802. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Dexatrim Caplets. TSDX 8293 Look at Her :30; TSDX 8303 Look at Her :30. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1803. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. 4 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1804. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim Caplets. TSDX 8343 Look at Her/Mortise :30. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1805. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim Caplets. TSDX 8303 Look at Her Alt. Rev :30. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1806. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8743 Scroll Today Teacher :30; TSDX 8813 Lost Weight Feel Great W/Pill Spill :30; TSDX 8783 Lost Weight Feel Great Rev. :30. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1807. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8753 I lost Weight and Feel Great :30. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1808. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 7223 No Diet Waters Caffeine Free :30. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1809. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 8553 Its Easier :30. 1988 (Box 107)
        - 1810. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 9815 Scroll Today :15. 1989 (Box 107)
        - 1811. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 9903 Lost Weight and Feel Great :30. 1989 (Box 107)
        - 1812. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Dexatrim. TSDX 9873 I lost Weight and Feel Great Rev.2 :30; TSDX 9883 I lost Weight and Feel Great Rev.3 :30. 1989 (Box 107)
      - Dexatrim (continued), 1989-1993 (Box 108)
        - 1813. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 9903 I lost Weight and Feel Great :30. 1989 (Box 108)
        - 1814. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. Scroll Today Ver.B :15. 1989 (Box 108)
        - 1815. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Dexatrim. 7 Spots. See Enclosed List. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1816. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 3133 Patti 13 W/Scroll Alt. V/O :30. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1817. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 3133 Patti 13 W/ Scroll Alt. V/o :30. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1818. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 3173 Pattie 13/9 Rev. W/Caplets :30. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1819. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 3183 Patti/Caplets Rev. CC :30. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1820. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 3103 Patti 13 Standing :30. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1821. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 3183 Pattie Caplets Rev. CC :30. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1822. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 3173 Patti 13/9 Rev. Caplets CC :30. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1823. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 1113 Universities Rev. :30. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1824. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 3193 Pattie Caplets Rev.2 :30. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1825. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 3193 Patti Caplets Rev.2 :30. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1826. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 3153 Patti 9/13 :30. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1827. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 3183 Patti Caplets Rev. :30. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1828. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 3173 Patti 13/9 Rev. Caplets CC :30. 1993 (Box 108)
        - 1829. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Dexatrim. TSDX 3103 Patti 13 standing :30. 1993 (Box 108)
      - Diar-aid, 1987-1993 (Box 109)
        - 1830. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Diar-Aid. XTVL 7143 Two Teaspoons Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 109)
        - 1831. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Diar-Aid. XTVL 7143 Two Teaspoons Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 109)
        - 1832. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Diar-Aid. TSDA 8243 Two Teaspoons Rev.9 :30; TSDA 8253 Two Teaspoons Rev.9 ABC :30. 1988 (Box 109)
        - 1833. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Diar-Aid. TSDA 8253 Two Teaspoons Rev.9 ABC :30. 1988 (Box 109)
        - 1834. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Diar-Aid. TSDA 8243 Two Teaspoons Rev.9 :30. 1988 (Box 109)
        - 1835. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Diar-Aid. TSDA 8243 two Teaspoons rev.9 :30. 1988 (Box 109)
        - 1836. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Diar-Aid. TSDA 3073 Works Fast :30. 1993 (Box 109)
        - 1837. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Diar-Aid. TSDA 3073 works Fast :30. 1993 (Box 109)
        - 1838. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Diar-Aid. TSDA 3073 Works Fast :30. 1993 (Box 109)
        - 1839. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Diar-Aid. TSDA 3073 Works Fast :30. 1993 (Box 109)
      - Essence of Galilee, 1987-1988
        - 1840. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Essence of Galilee. XYLC 7733 Sea of Galilee :30. 1987 (Box 109)
        - 1841. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Essence of Galilee. XYLC 7733 Sea of Galilee :30. 1987 (Box 109)
        - 1842. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Essence of Galilee. Sea of Galilee Vers.1. 1988 (Box 109)
      - Fiber Full, 1986-1988
        - 1843. Saatchi Saatchi & Compton. Thompson Medical. Fiber Full. By Nature :15. 1986 (Box 109)
        - 1844. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Fiber Full. XTVO 2012 By Nature :15. 1987 (Box 109)
        - 1845. Saatchi Saatchi & Compton. Thompson Medical. Fiber Full. XTVO 0303 By Nature Rev.1 Vers.1 :. 1988 (Box 109)
      - Fiber Full (continued), 1988 (Box 110)
        - 1846. Saatchi Saatchi & Compton. Thompson Medical. Fiber Full. XTVO 0203 By Nature Rev.1 Vers.1. 1988 (Box 110)
        - 1847. Saatchi Saatchi & Compton. Thompson Medical. Fiber Full. XTVO 0103 By Nature :25/:05. 1988 (Box 110)
        - 1848. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Fiber Full. XTVO 7015 Nature Rev. w/Super :15. 1988 (Box 110)
        - 1849. Saatchi Saatchi & Compton. Thompson Medical. Fiber Full. XTVO 1703 By Nature Dealer :26. 1988 (Box 110)
      - Lactogest, 1992
        - 1850. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Lactogest. TSLG 2115 pizza Non-New :15. 1992 (Box 110)
        - 1851. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Lactogest. TSLG 2115 pizza Non-New :15. 1992 (Box 110)
        - 1852. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Lactogest. TSLG 1085 pizza Rev. C Vers.5 :15. 1992 (Box 110)
      - NP-27, 1987-1991
        - 1853. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. NP-27. XTVK 7213 Foot :30. 1987 (Box 110)
        - 1854. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. NP-27. XTVK 7245 Burt Competitive :15. 1987 (Box 110)
        - 1855. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. NP-27. XTVK 7213 Foot :30; XTVK 7225 Foot Competitive :15; XTVK 7185 Foot :15. 1987 (Box 110)
        - 1856. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. NP-27. TSNP 9263 Foot Champion :30; TSNP 9275 Foot Champion :15; TSNP 9285 Burt Competitive Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 110)
        - 1857. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. NP-27. TSNP 9263 Foot Champion :30; TSNP 9275 Foot Champion :15; TSNP 9285 Burt Competitive Rev. :15. 1989 (Box 110)
        - 1858. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. NP-27. TSNP 1325 Tennis Rev. :15. 1991 (Box 110)
        - 1859. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. NP-27. TSNP 1295 Foot Champion Rev.2 :15. 1991 (Box 110)
        - 1860. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. NP-27. TSNP 1305 Tennis :15. 1991 (Box 110)
      - Sleepinal, 1987
        - 1861. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sleepinal. XTVS 7065 Doctors Choice :15. 1987 (Box 110)
        - 1862. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sleepinal. TSSL 7165 Doctors Choice/Product :15. 1987 (Box 110)
      - Sleepinal (continued), 1987-1992 (Box 111)
        - 1863. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sleepinal. Xtvs 7065 Doctors Choice :30. 1987 (Box 111)
        - 1864. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Sleepinal. TSSL 8175 Doctors Choice/Rev.2 :30. 1988 (Box 111)
        - 1865. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Sleepinal. TSSL 8175 Doctors Choice/Rev.2 :15. 1988 (Box 111)
        - 1866. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sleepinal Medicated Night Tea. TSMT 1175 Night Tea Introduction G Ver.D :15. 1992 (Box 111)
      - SlimFast, 1987
        - 1867. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Slim Fast. XTVS 1-7025 Pledge :15. 1987 (Box 111)
        - 1868. Saatchi Saatchi & Compton. Thompson Medical. Slim Fast. XTVS 0883 Pledge with Tag Rev. CBS/NBC Vers :30. 1987 (Box 111)
        - 1869. Thompson Medical. Slim Fast. XTVS 0883 Pledge W/Tag Rev. CBS/NBC Vers. :30. 1987 (Box 111)
      - Slim Mints, 1987
        - 1870. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Slim Mints. XTVZ 7035 Disappear Rev.2 :15. 1987 (Box 111)
        - 1871. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Slim Mints. XTVZ 7055 Disappear Rev.2 :15. 1987 (Box 111)
        - 1872. Saatchi Saatchi & Compton. Slim Mint. Disappear Nat'l & Walgreen Tag. Undated (Box 111)
        - 1873. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Slim Mints. XTVZ 7035 Disappear Rev.2 :15. 1987 (Box 111)
      - Sportscreme, 1987
        - 1874. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sportscreme Ice. XTVF 7173 Tennis Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 111)
        - 1875. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sportscreme. XTVF 7183 Workout/New Demo Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 111)
        - 1876. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sportscreme. XTVF 7193 Workout/New Product :30. 1987 (Box 111)
        - 1877. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sportscreme. Workout Vs. Ben Gay-New Mis :15. 1987 (Box 111)
        - 1878. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sportscreme. 4 spots. See Enclosed List. 1987 (Box 111)
        - 1879. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sportscreme Ice. XTVF 7173 Tennis Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 111)
      - Sportscreme (continued), 1987-1990 (Box 112)
        - 1880. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sportscreme. XTVF 7203 Workout/Revco Tag Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 112)
        - 1881. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sportscreme. End lice. XYLC 7623 Embarrassing Rev. Protection Master :30; XYLC 7605 Embarrassing Rev. Protection Master :15; XTVF 7173 Tennis Rev. :30. 1987 (Box 112)
        - 1882. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sportscream. XTVF 7065 Workout Vs. Ben Gay :15. 1987 (Box 112)
        - 1883. Laurence Charles Free & Lawson. Thompson Medical. Sportscreme. XTVF 7193 Workout/New Product :30. 1987 (Box 112)